PEDRO A. RODRIGUEZ O.



CONTACT

El Paraíso, Caracas Venezuela



+58 426 6313617 (WhatsApp) +58 424 2796488



pedroaro123@gmail.com



SKILLS

Ruby on Rails

NodeJS

Materialize

Bootstrap

JQuery

LANGUAGES

React Native

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced Computer scientist graduate, Full-Stack Web Developer and Teaching assistant with a demonstrated history of working in the higher education industry. Skilled in JavaScript, HTML5, Ruby on Rails, Mysql, React Native and Linux area. Currently working as Full Stack Web developer in Ruby on Rails at 300Dev Company.

WORK EXPERIENCE

300Dev / Full Stack Web Developer

JUNE 2019 - DECEMBER 2019, CARACAS, VE

Full Stack web developer, creating web applications in Ruby on Rails with many new technologies, including amazon web services.

Siscotel / Full Stack Web Developer

JANUARY 2019 - JUNE 2019, CARACAS, VE

I created a web application using many knowledges of now technologies, the app is called PMLS (Project Management Longitude Surveyors), in this one I used many amazon web services as S3 storage in buckets and lambda functions.

The Chain / Mobile and Web Developer

MARCH 2018 - 2019, CARACAS, VE

I developed a web application with NodeJS, and at the same time, through services, created a mobile application using React Native.

Universidad Central de Venezuela / Full Stack Web Developer JANUARY 2017 – JUNE 2019, CARACAS, VE

I developed an automated system named FORMINST. This system is used by professors of the Faculty of Sciences to carry out their training. Ruby on Rails knowledge was used as a Framework, and MySQL as DBMS.

EDUCATION

Universidad Central de Venezuela / Bachelor Degree in

Computer Science

2014 - 2019, CARACAS, VE

CERTIFICATIONS

Ruby on Rails Web Development / Johns Hopkins University COURSERA, 2019

English Business Communication / University of Washington COURSERA, SEP – OCT 2016